Register to The E.Y. Harburg Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Harburgiana, 1929-1968; Series II
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence on Musical Productions
      - Blue Holiday, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 162)
        - Roe, Stuart, 1955 Jan 20; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 162)
        - to Roe, Stuart, 1955 Apr 1; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 162)
        - to Lampkin, Charles P., 1963 Nov 11; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 162)
      - Finian's Rainbow, (stage: 1947)
        - Liebling, William, 1945 Dec 26; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Berman, Abraham L., 1946 Jan 23; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Kidd, Michael, 1947 Jan 10; telegram (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Hammerstein, Oscar, 1947 Jan 11; telegram (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Porter, Cole, 1947 Jan 13; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Taylor, Deems, 1947 Feb 7; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - MacKenna, Kenneth (Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer), 1947 Feb 20; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Watt, Mary, M. for The Richmond Times Dispatch, 1947 Mar 17; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - to Watt, Mary M., 1947 Mar 21; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Tarcher, Mary (Mrs. Jack D.), 1947 Feb 4; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - to Tarcher, Mary, 1947 Apr 2; photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Kaufman, Harry, 1947 Apr 21; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Francis, Robert (Drama Editor for The Billboard), 1947 Aug 27; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - O'Casey, Sean, 1947 Aug 31; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - to Harris, Lou, 1947 Nov 14; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Brown, Stephen [Hugh], 1947 Dec 10; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - to Brown, Stephen [Hugh], 1948 Jan 27; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Meltzer, Herman I. to Brown, Stephen [Hugh], 1948 Feb 4; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Brown, Stephen [Hugh] to Meltzer, Herman I., 1948 Feb 9; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Provence, Jean, 1948 Feb 12; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
          [See also: packet of correspondence to and from Rufus Atwood, in Box 5, Folder 31.]
        - Saidy, Fred, 1949 Aug; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - to Kelly, P.J., 1953 Mar 12; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Driver, D.[o]nn, 1953 Mar 19; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Kelly, P.J., 1957 Jul 23; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - [J]ubera, Paul, 1958 May 8; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Aborn, Louis H. (President, Tams-Witmark) to Rothberg, Marvin, 1959 Dec 3; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Dassin, Jules, 1959 Dec 19; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Colum, Padraic, 1960 May 18; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Michalowska, (Mrs.) Mira, 1960 Jun 2; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Windust, Irene, 1960 Jun 13; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Popper, Martin, 1960 Jun 16; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 163)
        - Morford, Richard, 1960 Jun 20; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Michalowska, (Mrs.) Mira, 1960 Aug 29; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - to Dassin, Jules, 1960 Nov 23; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Holland, Catherine, 1961 Jan 21; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Bridge, Peter, 1961 Jan 24; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - to Bridge, Peter, 1961 Jan 30; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Bridge, Peter, 1961 Feb 4; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Bridge, Peter, 1961 Feb 22; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Meltzer, Herman I., 1961 Mar 2; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Bridge, Peter, 1961 Mar 20; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Meltzer, Herman I., 1961 Mar 22; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Michalowska, (Mrs.) Mira, 1961 Apr 14; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - to Michalowska, (Mrs.) Mira, [1961 Apr ?]; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Michalowska, (Mrs.) Mira, 1961 Nov 6; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Kerwin, Robert W., 1962 Apr 17; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Vivanco, Moises, 1962 Apr 23; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Vivanco, Moises, 1962 Jun 27; carbon (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Michalowska, (Mrs.) Mira, 1963 Aug 5; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Aborn, Louis H. (President, Tams-Witmark) to Meltzer, Herman I., 1963 Oct 11; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Meltzer, Herman I., 1964 Feb 4; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Levine, Meyer to Goldstein [Winston], Helen, 1964 Feb 7; typed letter signed, draft (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Oppenheim, David J. to Meltzer, Herman I., 1968 Jul 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Weeks, Shirley S., 1968 Jul 28; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - to Weeks, Shirley S., [1968?]; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 164)
        - Buckminster, Harold (Princeton University), [no date]; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 164)
      - Flahooley, 1951 (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Siegler, Sylvia H. (Show-of-the-Month, Inc.) to Crawford, Cheryl, 1950 Jul 10; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Saidy, Fred, 1950 Aug 6; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Bird, Bonnie, 1951 Feb 19; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Katz, Charles J., 1951 Mar 1; telegram (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Massine, Stella, 1951 May [20?]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Massine, Stella, 1951 May 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Joseph, Betty, 1951 May 11; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Joseph, Betty, 1951 Jun 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Spindell, Lora, 1951 Jun 12; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - [?], Jay, [1951]; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Lester, Edwin, 1952 Jan 30; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Lester, Edwin, 1952 Feb 6; telegram (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Lester, Edwin, 1952 " 29; telegram (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Schacter, Harry, 1952 Mar 10; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Lester, Edwin, 1952 Mar 12; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Lester, Edwin, 1952 Mar 20; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Lester, Edwin, 1952 May 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - [Lester, Edwin], 1952 Sep 8; telegram (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Fain, Sammy, 1953 Feb 19; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - to Pascal, Ernest, 1953 Mar 27; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 165)
        - Frank, Benno, 1960 Aug 28; telegram (Box 21, Folder 165)
      - Jamaica, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - to Nadal, Laura, 1953 Feb 12; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - to Freed, Arthur, 1957 May 23; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - Rosner, Elsie to Hannah Epstein, 1957 Nov 26; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - Merrick, David, 1958 Oct 31; telegram (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - Frank, Benno, 1959 Oct 22; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - to Frank, Benno, 1959 Oct 22; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - Frank, Benno, 1959 Nov 14; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - Frank, Benno, 1960 Feb 3; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 166)
        - Frank, Benno, 1960 Jul 25; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 166)
      - The Happiest Girl in the World, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 167)
        (also "Orpheus" & "Lysistrata")
        - Saidy, Fred, [1954-1955?]; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Hecht, Ben, 1954 Jun 27; photocopy (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to Hecht, Ben, 1955 Jun 27; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Trumbo, Dalton, 1957 Mar 25; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Guthrie, Tyrone, [1958?] Oct 10; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Crawford, Cheryl, 1958 Sep 24; carbon, signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Thorson, Marjorie, 1959 Apr 3; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - MacKenna, Kenneth, 1959 Apr 23; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to Minnelli, Vincente, [no date]; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Saidy, Fred, 1960; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Drake, Alfred, 1960 May 17; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Ritchard, Cyril, 1960 Sep 23; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to Ritchard, Cyril, 1960; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to Cape-Codders [unidentified], 1960 Nov 15; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Arlen, Harold, 1961 Jan 16; telegram (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Cooke, F.O., 1961 Feb 5; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Graham, Ronny, 1961 Apr 3; telegram (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Martin, Mary & Halliday, Richard, 1961 Apr 3; telegram (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Meyers, Henry, 1961 Apr 3; telegram (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Rodgers, Dick, 1961 Apr 3; telegram (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Seitz, Dan, [1961 Apr 3?]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Styne, Jule, 1961 Apr 3; telegram (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to Dash, Tom, 1961 Apr 7; carbon, signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Fisher, Steve, 1961 Apr 14; carbon, signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Gallagher, Buell G., 1961 Apr 17; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to Sullivan, Ed, 1961 Apr 25; carbon (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Loesser, Frank, 1961 Apr 28; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - [Poyton?], 1961 Jun 1; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - to De Vol, Frank, 1961 Jun 21; carbon, signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Dorso, Richard, 1961 Jun 22; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Asher, Adele R. (Mrs. Arthur O.), 1961 Jun 27; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - De Vol, Frank, 1961 Aug 2; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Guber, Lee (producer of show), 1961 Aug 29; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Guber, Lee, 1964 Mar 5; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Limbacher, James L., Dearborn Public Library, 1964 Nov 24; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
        - Limbacher, James L., 1965 Jan 14; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 167)
      - Gay Purree, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - Saperstein, Henry G., 1961 Aug 2; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - to Saperstein, Henry G. (Hank), [1961 Aug ?]; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - Bricker, Seymour to Berman, Abraham L., 1961 Aug 16; carbon (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - Saperstein, Henry G. (Hank), 1961 Aug 24; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - Jablonski, Edward, 1961 Oct 31; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 168)
        - Garland, Judy, [1962]; telegram (Box 21, Folder 168)
      - Finian's Rainbow
        (Animation: 1954-1955; Motion picture: 1967)
        - to Agnew, Neil, 1953 Sep 16; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Polaski, Perry M., 1954 Mar 8; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Saidy, Fred, 1954 Mar 12; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Binder, Maurice (Placid Productions, Inc.), 1954 Nov 19; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Murray, Lyn (vocal arranger), [1954-1955?]; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Sabinson, Lee, 1955 Jun 28; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Heller, Walter E., President, W.E. Heller Co. to Schacter, Harry, President, Banner-Whitehall Corp., 1955 Oct 7; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to [?], Sam, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Lazar, Irving, 1957 Apr 17; typed letter signed, draft & carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Buchman, Sidney, [1958?]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Buchman, Sidney, [1958?] Oct 10; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Coslow, Sam, 1958 Oct 22; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Coslow, Sam [postscript to typed letter from J.R. Wallis, Assoc., British Picture Corp., Inc., to Max Kester, Esq.], 1958 Nov 14; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Buchman, Sidney, 1958 Nov 21; carbon (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - [Buchman], Sidney, [1958 Nov ?]; telegram (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Buchman, Sidney, [1958] Nov 26; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Buchman, Sidney, [1959] Jan 1; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Buchman, Sidney, [1959] Jan 13; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Buchman, Sidney, [1959?]; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Gordon, Mike, 1959 Dec 26; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Davis, Ossie to [Gordon?], Mike, [1960?]; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Gomber, Sy, 1963 Oct 16; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Washburn, John L. (Writer-producer, MPO Prod., Inc.), 1965 May 25; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
          (Enclosure: cost estimate for film production & resume of producer, Charles S. Dubin)
        - Washburn, John L., 1966 May 5; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
          (Enclosure: correspondence with Harold Hecht, prospectus for MPO production of Finian, & resume)
        - to Lane, Burton, [1967?]; typed letter signed, draft (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Lane, Burton, 1967 Jan 19; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Lane, Burton, 1967 Feb 12; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Pine, Ralph (Managing editor, DBS Publications), 1967 Apr 28; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Landon, Joseph to Lane, Burton, 1967 May 23; typed letter signed, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Lane, Burton to Landon, Joseph, 1967 May 25; typed letter signed, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Freeman, Joel, 1967 Aug 11; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Line, Huguette, 1967 Oct 25; telegram (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Saidy, Fred to Writers Guild of America, West, Inc., 1967 Oct 30; carbon (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Writers Guild of America, 1967 Nov 1; photocopy & carbon (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Dorfman, Mary, Credits Administrator, Writers Guild of America, West, Inc., 1967 Nov 29; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Landon, Joseph, 1968 Feb 22; carbon, signed & photocopy (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Coppola, Francis, 1968 Mar 7; typed letter, draft & carbon, signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Hyman, Kenneth, Warner Bros.-Seven Arts Studio, 1968 Mar 28; carbon (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Grimes, Tammy, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Maitland, Mike [John K.], President, Warner Bros.-Seven Arts Records, Inc., 1968 Jun 17; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Saidy, Fred, 1968 Jun 19; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - Hickey, Neil, N.Y. Bureau Chief, T.V. Guide, [1968?] Jul 15; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 169)
        - to Langner, Philip, 1965 Feb 24; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel W., 1965 Apr 7; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to K. & W. [Keith Waterhouse & Willis Hall?], 1965 May 1; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Marshall, Armina to Langner, Philip & Schenker, Joel, 1965 May 7; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to Marshall, Langner, Schenker, 1965 May 25; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Meth, Max M., 1965 Jun 12; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Myers, Henry, 1965 Jun 25; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
      - Darling of the Day, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to [Langner], Phil, [Marshall], Armina, [Schenker], Joel & [Styne], Jule, 1965 Sep 14; carbon, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel to Gregson, Richard, 1965 Nov 24; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1965 Nov 26; memo, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Myers, Henry, [1965?] Dec 29; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1966 Jun 28; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1966 Sep 30; memo, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to [Schenker, Joel?], [1967?]; autograph letter signed, draft (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1967 Feb 8; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1967 Mar 2; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to Schenker, Joel, [1967 Aug?]; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1967 Aug 28; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1967 Aug 29; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Miller, Carl S., Editor, Chappell & Co. Inc., 1967 Nov 9; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Solomon, Artie (for Arthur Cantor), 1967 Nov 17; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Fitelson, William H., 1967 Nov 27; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - [Myers, Henry?], [1967?]; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - [Harburg, Edelaine?], 1967; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Myers, Henry, 1967; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Endicott, H. P., 1967 Dec 1; memo, photocopy (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Styne, Jule, 1967 Dec 4; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to "Colleagues, of Married Alive", 1967 Dec 5; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to Johnson, Nunnally, 1967 Dec 8; typed letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to Johnson, Nunnally, 1967 Dec 8; carbon [incomplete] (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Styne, Jule, 1967 Dec 20; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to Willman, Noel, 1967 Dec 26; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Adams, Stanley, President, ASCAP, 1968 Jan 26; typed letter, carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Linhart, Barbara & Joe, 1968 Jan 26; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Kingsley, Sidney, President, The Dramatists Guild Council, 1968 Jan 26; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Styne, Jule, 1968 Jan 26; typed letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Marshall, Armina, [1968 Jan 27?]; authograph letter (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Schenker, Joel, 1968 Jan 27; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - [Fields?], Dorothy & [?], Charlotte, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Gilford, Madeleine & Jack, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Hayward, Leland, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Hirson, Roger, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Johnson, Nunnally, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Myers, Henry, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Rae, Charlotte, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Saidy, Fred, 1968 Jan 27; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Fain, Sammy, 1968 Jan 28; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Lahr, [Bert & Mrs.], 1968 Jan 28; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Routledge, Patricia, [1968 Jan ?]; telegram (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - to Daniel, Clifton, Managing Editor, The New York Times, 1968 Feb 13; carbon (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - [to Styne, Jule?], [1968?]; authograph letter, draft (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - Daniel, Clifton, 1968 Feb 20; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - [Schenker?], Joel, [1968 Feb-Mar?]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
        - [Price, Vincent?], [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 170)
      - "Blue Star" or "Jerusalem" (Box 21, Folder 171)
        [Unproduced musical with book by Joshua Logan. Songs were to be written by E.Y. Harburg and Burton Lane. See also: Box 19, Folder 145 for Logan's script dated 1961 May 31]
        - Logan, Joshua, 1961 Jul 13; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to Logan, Joshua, 1961 Jul 21; copy, draft (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to Logan, Joshua, 1961 Jul 26; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to Logan, Joshua, 1961 Jul 26; photocopy, draft (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - [Palca?], Alfred, 1961 Aug 4; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - Lane, Burton, 1961 Aug 6; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - Logan, Joshua, 1961 Aug 30; autograph letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to Logan, Joshua, 1961 Sep 11; carbon (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to Lane, Burton, 1961 Sep 11; carbon (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to [Palca?], Alfred, 1961 Sep 11; carbon (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - Logan, Joshua, 1961 Sep 14; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - Lane, Burton, 1962 Sep 11; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 171)
        - to [?], Larry, 1968 Jul 2; autograph letter signed, carbon (Box 21, Folder 171)
      - [Lonely Stage (1962)] (Box 21, Folder 172)
        - Chaplin, Saul, 1962 Feb 10; telegram (Box 21, Folder 172)
        - to Chaplin, Saul, 1962 Feb 11; carbon (Box 21, Folder 172)
        - Chaplin, Saul, 1962 Feb 23; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 172)
        - to Chaplin, Saul, [1962?]; carbon (Box 21, Folder 172)
          (Enclosure: 2nd chorus & alternate lines for "I Could Go On Singing"]
        - Chaplin, Saul, 1962 Apr 9; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 172)
        - Chaplin, Saul, 1962 Apr 12; typed letter signed (Box 21, Folder 172)
        - Millar, Stuart & Turman, Lawrence to Arlen, Harold, 1962 Aug 27; copy (Box 21, Folder 172)
    - General Correspondence
      - to Abramson, Dr. [?], 1955 Jul 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - to Alpert, Norman, 1955 Apr 25; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Alstone, Alex, 1967 Nov 14; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Anders, Jean, 1951 Jun 11; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - to Anders, Jean, 1951 Jun 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Arlen, Harold, 1940 Jan 23; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - to Arlen, Harold, 1952 Mar 27; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Arlen, Harold, 1952 Apr 1; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Arlen, Harold, 1952 Aug 1; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Arlen, Harold, [1952?]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - to Arlen, Harold, [no date]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Aronson, Boris, 1935 Jan 22; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 173)
      - Baird, Bill, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Baussan, Robert, 1953 Jan 7; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Beckwith, Ethel, [? Aug 12]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Behrman, Sam, [no date]; telegram (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Behrman, Sam N., 1959 Feb 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Behrman, Sam N., 1961 Oct 12; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Behrman, Sam N., 1966 Apr 18; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Benjamin, Burton, 1963 Nov 11; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Berman, Abraham, 1935 Jun 8; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Berman, Abraham, 1935 Oct 11; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)